In this world...
Is the destiny of mankind controlled by some transcendental entity or law?
Is it like the hand of God hovering above?
At least it is true...
...that man has no control, even over his own will.
Why does Griffith value you so much?
There's no reason...
...in particular.
Do you really need a reason...
...each time I decide to lay
my life on the line for you?
Feel no shame about shape
Weather changes their phrase
Even mother will show you another way
So put your glasses on
Nothing will be wrong
There's no blame. There's no fame
It's up to you
The first words should be found
Whatever holds you back
I...
...can...
I can get it off
Tell me what...
Tell me what you want
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Don't know why you're afraid
Tell me what...
Tell me what you'd say
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Too late...
It's too late
Conspiracy
All right!
Stretch out the rest of the ropes!
Any sign of the enemy?
Nothing at all.
Even if hundreds or thousands
of the enemy attempt an attack...
The elite of the valiant Blue Whale
Heavy Assault Knights are here.
No one can set one foot in
a stronghold under our guard!
Listen...
You must always be on your guard in war.
Do not cease to be vigilant!
Yes, sir!
Our commander is unusually alert.
Yeah, it's because he's been
given such an important job.
I suppose he cannot help but be enthusiastic.
Is it from Guts?
No doubt.
It's the signal for the next phase!
Good!
Let's move.
Enemy raid!
What?
An enemy raid?
Enemy raid!
Let's go!
Ready!
Enemy raid!
They finally showed their faces!
Aye, sir!
Well, fire the cannons into
the center of their formation!
Sir, it is impossible
to reach them at this distance.
Then send out the whole unit
and tear those rotten kids apart!
Yes, sir!
Hold on a minute!
This is their trap!
They must realize how difficult
it would be to destroy this stronghold.
So they are plotting
to lead us out into the field!
How foolish they are!
Such cheap tricks
are of no use against Sir Adon...
...the most resourceful
commander in the Tudor army.
Now what are we supposed to do?
Ignore them.
What?
Let them buzz around as they like!
All right!
It's time to get moving!
Griffith!
I've confirmed that all
the Raiders have crossed the river!
Excellent!
Let us vanish from the sight of the enemy!
It looks like they're pulling back!
It's not worth risking their lives
to attack this impregnable stronghold!
Message!
Open the gate!
What's happened?
The general will be visiting this castle
regarding an important operation!
R-Really?
I'll pass the information
to your commander directly!
Certainly!
W-What's this?
W-What's the meaning of this?
They snuck in from the rear gate!
They disappeared and
then burst in from the back!
What a dirty trick!
Blow them all apart!
Y-Yes, sir!
We'll repel them with our entire force!
Should we send the signal now?
No, first we secure their way in!
It's an enemy raid!
Bring all the bridge
guards back into the castle!
Griffith...
We shall wait for the signal.
Can't he be quick about it?
I wonder why he puts so much faith in Guts...
What's going on?
Why did you open the gate?
Now!
Yes, sir!
W-What was that?
Griffith!
Rush the front gate of the castle, quickly!
Shit!
Do they think they can
succeed with such a small number?
I, Sir Adon, shall put
an end to their lives personally!
The enemy is breaking through the front!
Damn it!
What sneaky tactics,
charging in from both sides like that!
We're caught between
the two groups. It's out of our control!
Give us your next command, sir!
Retreat!
But...
My brain is key to the Tudor Empire!
I must avoid dying in vain here!
That's our commander!
You had a raft prepared just in case!
I am always prepared!
It is a commander's duty!
C-Commander!
Commander!
Please, take us with you.
Please!
Get away!
How outrageous of you!
This raft is a precious heirloom...
...that has been handed down
through the Coborlwitz family!
Remove your armor!
You can all swim!
You did well.
I just followed your orders.
We did it!
Finally, we drove
a wedge into Tudor territory.
We've opened the pass leading to Doldrey.
Oh boy, that was a long walk!
First I'll feed my stomach
with a sumptuous meal...
...and then I'll have a well-deserved rest!
Y-Your Grace, General Boscone!
What happened to Fort Brax?
W-Well, our enemy
was so devious that...
...even I was inferior in terms
of underhanded trickery, sir.
So did you just roll over
and surrender the fortress?
No, I deliberately withdrew and
let them occupy the fort temporarily...
...to give us ample time to regroup, sir...
Enough lies!
Do you comprehend how important
that fort was to deployment?
W-Well, sir...
I'm warning you. This is
the last time I will support you!
Lord Boscone...
A warrior must always follow
the principles of honor and justice!
This is true now and always!
Yes, sir!
This time, I shall put an end
to them with the secret tactics...
...that have been passed down
the Coborlwitz family for 500 years!
No doubt about it!
It's 500 years now?
Not quarreling with some evil design...
Not straying from virtue...
Sacrifice thyself ceaselessly...
Render your services to
our fief for peace and security...
The title of count is
bestowed upon thee...
Place thy flesh and heart in heaven.
Separate thyself from falsehood...
Uphold the law, know the subjects...
Be valiant, and with due
majesty, advance the war.
Stand prepared for thy foe with
due thirst for battle and fear not.
Despite the machinations of
thy foes who march upon thee...
...the duly appointed count
of our glorious kingdom of Midland...
He has become a count...
Say, did you hear about it?
Sir Griffith was awarded the title of count!
I've heard that too!
He's so handsome!
I'm jealous because he's so attractive
and more graceful than any woman!
Not only that...
...he is the greatest swordsman in the kingdom...
...and commands the strongest army!
He is far more classy
than those awkward nobles...
...and he has so much
presence and elegance!
True, compared to him, those
court ministers are all rude and rough.
The poor officials just
can't compare to Sir Griffith!
You women!
You should not speak of such things!
W-We are sorry, Your Excellency!
Those gossipers...
General Julius...
What use is yelling if your
voice echoes throughout the court?
You look very
displeased for some reason.
It makes me wonder what is wrong.
It is no concern of yours!
Oh, yes.
Did Your Grace
happen to learn about...
...the king's escort
for the upcoming fall hunt?
In that matter...
...my unit, the White Dragon Knights,
are regularly assigned to the task.
What is your point?
The Band of the Hawk was requested
as escort by imperial decree.
T-That cannot be!
It is reliable information...
Nonsense!
The fall hunt is an important
event that allows the king...
...to promote friendly relations
between feudal lords.
Our best knights, the White
Dragons, are the only ones...
...who are allowed to serve
the king in that honorable assignment.
How could those upstart
thieves take that from us?
What is His Majesty thinking?
Will you allow this affair to take place?
What do you mean?
The White Dragons were reputed
to be the strongest unit in the kingdom.
Nevertheless, their glory
has turned insignificant...
...due to the Band of the Hawk's rise.
Y-You...
This is a rumor.
As I say, it is a rumor within the court.
It is an unmistakable fact that
the Band of the Hawk is invincible.
There is no sign that the
disturbances of war will subside soon.
Therefore, that man will keep winning
honors through his military exploits.
Additionally, His Majesty highly
values that boy, as you can see.
So while I don't know how
he won His Majesty's favor...
If things go badly, that boy
might become a general...
Do not talk nonsense!
I would never permit it!
It is unheard of, some upstart
mercenary becoming a general!
That bastard could be a general like I am?
That man of common origins
would be on the same level as me?
Well, I just mentioned the
possibility. That which could be...
I won't allow it!
I absolutely will not allow it!
However, some danger always
lies in the act of hunting...
...despite the fact it is an imperial event.
You never know what kind of
beasts hide within the woods...
What are you trying to say?
Of course, not only are the beasts dangerous...
...but so are the stray arrows that may
have been launched at the beasts.
A stray arrow?
And a nastily-poisoned stray arrow at that...
If you mean...
A stray arrow, General.
A stray arrow...
Interesting!
It would be a proper death
for a man of common birth!
Looking back, the morning comes.
Don't find your face in your glass.
Take the moonlight by the tail.
It's a rainy sight. You're shading.
What is that?
It's just the same.
What is trying your crown?
I'm spending my glass, walking back.
So wear my glass. You're fading.
I'm waiting so long.
I'm waiting...